p1 = [
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"﻿alumin","osnova2":"v","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"bezvr","osnova2":"dan","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"bezvr","osnova2":"dno","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"bezvr","osnova2":"dnost","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"b","osnova2":"da","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"b","osnova2":"dan","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"b","osnova2":"dno","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"b","osnova2":"l","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"b","osnova2":"liti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"b","osnova2":"ljeti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"b","osnova2":"s","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"bl","osnova2":"d","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"bl","osnova2":"djeti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"br","osnova2":"g","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"c","osnova2":"diti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"c","osnova2":"l","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"c","osnova2":"lo","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"c","osnova2":"na","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"c","osnova2":"niti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"c","osnova2":"p","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"c","osnova2":"piti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"c","osnova2":"pljenje","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"c","osnova2":"v","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"c","osnova2":"vka","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"cr","osnova2":"vo","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"cv","osnova2":"će","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"cv","osnova2":"t","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"cv","osnova2":"tak","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"četverod","osnova2":"lan","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"d","osnova2":"liti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"d","osnova2":"ljenje","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"d","osnova2":"ta","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"d","osnova2":"te","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"d","osnova2":"tetički","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"d","osnova2":"tetika","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"d","osnova2":"tni","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"dl","osnova2":"to","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"dod","osnova2":"liti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"don","osnova2":"ti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"dv","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"dvod","osnova2":"lan","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"financ","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"garson","osnova2":"ra","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"gluhon","osnova2":"m","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"gluhosl","osnova2":"p","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"gn","osnova2":"zdo","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"gr","osnova2":"h","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"dan","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"izv","osnova2":"stiti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"jednod","osnova2":"lan","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"kar","osnova2":"ra","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"kasn","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"kl","osnova2":"šta","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"kol","osnova2":"vka","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"kor","osnova2":"n","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"kor","osnova2":"nje","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"kr","osnova2":"štati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"kukur","osnova2":"k","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"kukur","osnova2":"kanje","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"kukur","osnova2":"kati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"kukur","osnova2":"knuti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"kvoc","osnova2":"nt","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"l","osnova2":"čiti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"l","osnova2":"čnica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"l","osnova2":"čničin","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"l","osnova2":"čnički","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"l","osnova2":"čnik","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"l","osnova2":"čnikov","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"l","osnova2":"gati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"l","osnova2":"k","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"l","osnova2":"n","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"l","osnova2":"no","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"l","osnova2":"nost","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"l","osnova2":"p","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"l","osnova2":"piti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"l","osnova2":"po","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"l","osnova2":"rica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"l","osnova2":"ričar","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"l","osnova2":"ričarev","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"l","osnova2":"ričarka","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"l","osnova2":"ričarov","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"l","osnova2":"ričarski","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"l","osnova2":"s","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"l","osnova2":"ska","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"l","osnova2":"vati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"l","osnova2":"vi","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"l","osnova2":"vo","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"litan","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"lit","osnova2":"v","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"m","osnova2":"h","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"m","osnova2":"njati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"m","osnova2":"šalica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"m","osnova2":"šati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"ml","osnova2":"čni","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"ml","osnova2":"ko","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"napr","osnova2":"d","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"nesv","osnova2":"st","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"nevr","osnova2":"me","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"n","osnova2":"dan","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"n","osnova2":"kati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"n","osnova2":"m","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"n","osnova2":"mo","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"obav","osnova2":"st","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"od","osnova2":"lo","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"od","osnova2":"vati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"oduv","osnova2":"k","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"osm","osnova2":"h","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"oždr","osnova2":"biti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"pac","osnova2":"nt","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"pac","osnova2":"ntica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"pac","osnova2":"ntičin","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"pac","osnova2":"ntov","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"pac","osnova2":"ntski","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"p","osnova2":"sak","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"p","osnova2":"tao","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"pob","osnova2":"diti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"podn","osnova2":"ti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"podr","osnova2":"tlo","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"pol","osnova2":"vati (se)","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"posl","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"posl","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"posl","osnova2":"podne","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"posl","osnova2":"podnevni","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"pov","osnova2":"st","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"prem","osnova2":"r","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"prem","osnova2":"rka","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"pr","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"pr","osnova2":"ći","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"pr","osnova2":"dlog","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"pr","osnova2":"dložni","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"pr","osnova2":"laz","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"pr","osnova2":"nos","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"pr","osnova2":"podne","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"pr","osnova2":"podnevni","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"pr","osnova2":"titi","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"pr","osnova2":"voz","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"prim","osnova2":"titi","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"pripov","osnova2":"st","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"pripov","osnova2":"tka","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"prom","osnova2":"niti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"propov","osnova2":"d","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"propov","osnova2":"dati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"razgov","osnova2":"tan","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"razgov","osnova2":"tno","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"razgov","osnova2":"tnost","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"razum","osnova2":"vati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"redosl","osnova2":"d","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"r","osnova2":"č","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"r","osnova2":"čki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"r","osnova2":"čni","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"r","osnova2":"dak","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"r","osnova2":"ka","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"r","osnova2":"šiti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"r","osnova2":"tko","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"r","osnova2":"tkost","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"s","osnova2":"čanj","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"sl","osnova2":"diti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"sl","osnova2":"p","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"sl","osnova2":"po","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"sm","osnova2":"h","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"sm","osnova2":"šak","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"sn","osnova2":"g","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"sn","osnova2":"žiti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"spr","osnova2":"da","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"sr","osnova2":"da","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"sr","osnova2":"mski","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"st","osnova2":"g","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"st","osnova2":"na","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"str","osnova2":"lac","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"str","osnova2":"lčev","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"sv","osnova2":"ća","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"sv","osnova2":"ćnjak","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"sv","osnova2":"st","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"sv","osnova2":"t","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"sv","osnova2":"tao","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"sv","osnova2":"tliti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"sv","osnova2":"tlo","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"širokobr","osnova2":"ški","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"t","osnova2":"kom","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"t","osnova2":"lo","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"T","osnova2":"lovo","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"t","osnova2":"lovski","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"t","osnova2":"sak","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"t","osnova2":"sto","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"trod","osnova2":"lan","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"umr","osnova2":"ti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"un","osnova2":"ti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"upotr","osnova2":"biti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"usl","osnova2":"d","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"usp","osnova2":"vati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"uv","osnova2":"k","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"v","osnova2":"će","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"v","osnova2":"nac","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"v","osnova2":"st","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"vr","osnova2":"dan","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"vr","osnova2":"diti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"vr","osnova2":"dno","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"vr","osnova2":"dnost","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"vr","osnova2":"me","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"zal","osnova2":"piti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"zapov","osnova2":"d","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"z","osnova2":"vati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"zv","osnova2":"r","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"zv","osnova2":"zda","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"ždr","osnova2":"be","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"ždr","osnova2":"biti se","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["ije","je"],"osnova":"ždr","osnova2":"lo","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"bd","osnova2":"ti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"bezos","osnova2":"ćajan","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"bezos","osnova2":"ćajno","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"bezos","osnova2":"ćajnost","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"bil","osnova2":"žnica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"bil","osnova2":"žničin","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"bil","osnova2":"žnički","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"bil","osnova2":"žnik","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"bil","osnova2":"žnikov","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"b","osnova2":"lina","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"b","osnova2":"logorica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"b","osnova2":"logorični","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"b","osnova2":"lokošćanski","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"b","osnova2":"loruski","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"b","osnova2":"žati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"bl","osnova2":"dilo","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"bogin","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"bol","osnova2":"ti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"branitel","osnova2":"v","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"bro","osnova2":"vni","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"brzinom","osnova2":"r","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"buđen","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"cijukan","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"c","osnova2":"dilo","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"c","osnova2":"lina","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"c","osnova2":"lovit","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"c","osnova2":"lovito","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"c","osnova2":"lovitost","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"c","osnova2":"pivo","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"c","osnova2":"včica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"crn","osnova2":"ti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"crven","osnova2":"ti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"cvil","osnova2":"ti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"cv","osnova2":"ćarna","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"cv","osnova2":"ćarnica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"cv","osnova2":"tača","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"cv","osnova2":"tić","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"čekan","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"češljan","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"četverom","osnova2":"sečni","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"četveror","osnova2":"čan","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"četveros","osnova2":"d","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"čin","osnova2":"nica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"čov","osnova2":"k","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"desetl","osnova2":"će","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"desetom","osnova2":"sečni","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"devetom","osnova2":"sečni","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"dil","osnova2":"m","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"d","osnova2":"ca","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"d","osnova2":"čačić","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"d","osnova2":"čačićev","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"d","osnova2":"čački","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"d","osnova2":"čak","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"d","osnova2":"čakov","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"d","osnova2":"čji","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"d","osnova2":"d","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"d","osnova2":"dov","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"d","osnova2":"dovina","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"d","osnova2":"latnost","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"d","osnova2":"litelj","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"d","osnova2":"lo","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"d","osnova2":"lotvoran","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"d","osnova2":"lotvorno","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"d","osnova2":"lotvornost","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"d","osnova2":"lovati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"d","osnova2":"l","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"d","osnova2":"ljiv","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"d","osnova2":"ljivost","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"d","osnova2":"telina","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"d","osnova2":"tešce","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"d","osnova2":"tinjstvo","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"d","osnova2":"vac","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"d","osnova2":"vica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"d","osnova2":"vičanski","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"d","osnova2":"vičin","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"d","osnova2":"vojački","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"d","osnova2":"vojčica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"d","osnova2":"vojčičin","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"d","osnova2":"vojčin","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"d","osnova2":"vojka","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"dod","osnova2":"ljivati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"događan","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"dokol","osnova2":"nica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"dokol","osnova2":"nka","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"dol","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"dos","osnova2":"tljiv","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"dos","osnova2":"tljivo","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"dos","osnova2":"tljivost","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"dosl","osnova2":"dan","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"dosl","osnova2":"dno","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"dosl","osnova2":"dnost","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"doživ","osnova2":"ti ","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"družen","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"drvl","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"dubinom","osnova2":"r","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"dv","osnova2":"sto","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"dv","osnova2":"stoti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"dvo","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"dvo","osnova2":"zičan","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"dvom","osnova2":"sečni","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"dvor","osnova2":"čan","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"dvos","osnova2":"d","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"dvot","osnova2":"dni","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"fijukan","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"fotokopiran","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"gd","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"gd","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"gd","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"gd","osnova2":"kad","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"gd","osnova2":"koji","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"gd","osnova2":"što","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"gd","osnova2":"što","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"gd","osnova2":"tko","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"gledatel","osnova2":"v","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"gor","osnova2":"ti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"govoren","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"grabl","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"grobl","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"gus","osnova2":"nica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"ht","osnova2":"ti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"hvalosp","osnova2":"v","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"inžen","osnova2":"r","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"inžen","osnova2":"rka","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"inžen","osnova2":"rkin","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"inžen","osnova2":"rov","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"inžen","osnova2":"rski","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"in","osnova2":"kcija","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"isel","osnova2":"nica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"isel","osnova2":"ničin","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"isel","osnova2":"nik","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"istraživan","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"izdan","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"iznenađen","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"izv","osnova2":"šćivati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"izv","osnova2":"štavati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"jačan","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"ja","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"jan","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"jan","osnova2":"ći","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"jan","osnova2":"tina","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"jan","osnova2":"vački","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"javnobil","osnova2":"žnički","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"cati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"čati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"dan","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"dan","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"danaest","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"danaesterac","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"danaestero","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"danaesti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"danput","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"dinac","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"dini","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"dinica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"diničin","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"dino","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"dnačen","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"dnak","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"dnako","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"dnakost","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"dni","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"dnina","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"dninski","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"dnodimenzijski","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"dnodimenzionalni","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"dnogodišnjak","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"dnogodišnjakinja","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"dnogodišnji","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"dno","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"dnokatni","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"dnokatnica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"dnokratan","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"dnokrevetni","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"dnom","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"dnom","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"dnoredan","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"dnor","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"dnos","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"dnoslov","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"dnosoban","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"dnostavan","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"dnostavno","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"dnostavnost","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"dnostih","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"dnostruk","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"dnot","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"dren","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"drilica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"dva","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"ftin","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"knuti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"la","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"len","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"lo","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"lovnik","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"r","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"ruzalemski","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"sen","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"senski","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"senji","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"sti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"tra","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"zero","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"zgra","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"zičac","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"zičak","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"zičast","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"zičav","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"zičavost","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"zični","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"zik","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"zikoslovac","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"zikoslovka","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"zikoslovkin","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"zikoslovl","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"zikoslovni","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"ž","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"žinac","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"kamen","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"kastan","osnova2":"te","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"kinopro","osnova2":"kcija","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"kinopro","osnova2":"ktor","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"ko","osnova2":"kakav","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"ko","osnova2":"šta","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"kokodakan","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"kol","osnova2":"no","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"kopl","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"korišten","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"kral","osnova2":"vstvo","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"kral","osnova2":"žnica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"kukurikan","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"kutom","osnova2":"r","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"lakov","osnova2":"ran","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"lakov","osnova2":"rno","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"lakov","osnova2":"rnost","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"let","osnova2":"lica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"let","osnova2":"ti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"lišavan","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"lizan","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"l","osnova2":"karna","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"l","osnova2":"karnica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"l","osnova2":"karničin","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"l","osnova2":"karnički","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"l","osnova2":"karnik","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"l","osnova2":"karnikov","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"l","osnova2":"pilo","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"l","osnova2":"pota","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"l","osnova2":"stve","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"l","osnova2":"šnjak","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"l","osnova2":"tni","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"l","osnova2":"to","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"l","osnova2":"tovati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"l","osnova2":"vak","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"l","osnova2":"vakinja","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"l","osnova2":"vakinjin","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"l","osnova2":"vakov","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"l","osnova2":"vaonica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"man","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"medv","osnova2":"d","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"medv","osnova2":"dić","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"mijaukan","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"mišl","osnova2":"n","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"m","osnova2":"hur","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"m","osnova2":"njač","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"m","osnova2":"njačica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"m","osnova2":"njačičin","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"m","osnova2":"njačnica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"m","osnova2":"ra","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"m","osnova2":"riti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"m","osnova2":"sec","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"m","osnova2":"sečina","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"m","osnova2":"sečno","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"m","osnova2":"sto","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"ml","osnova2":"kara","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"ml","osnova2":"karnica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"ml","osnova2":"tski","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"množen","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"mukan","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"na","osnova2":"sti se","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"nam","osnova2":"ravati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"nam","osnova2":"snik","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"nam","osnova2":"štaj","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"nasel","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"nasil","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"nat","osnova2":"can","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"nat","osnova2":"catelj","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"nat","osnova2":"catel","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"nat","osnova2":"cateljica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"nat","osnova2":"cateljičin","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"nat","osnova2":"cateljski","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"nat","osnova2":"cati se","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"nat","osnova2":"čaj","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"natkol","osnova2":"nka","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"nazdravl","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"nazivl","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"nazivoslovl","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"ned","osnova2":"lja","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"ned","osnova2":"ljiv","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"ned","osnova2":"ljivo","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"ned","osnova2":"ljivost","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"ned","osnova2":"ljni","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"negd","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"neodgo","osnova2":"n","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"neodgo","osnova2":"no","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"neodgo","osnova2":"nost","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"nepob","osnova2":"div","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"nepob","osnova2":"divo","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"nepob","osnova2":"divost","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"neprom","osnova2":"njiv","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"neprom","osnova2":"njivo","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"neprom","osnova2":"njivost","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"nesv","osnova2":"snost","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"neum","osnova2":"ren","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"neum","osnova2":"reno","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"neum","osnova2":"renost","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"njakan","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"n","osnova2":"gov","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"n","osnova2":"govati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"n","osnova2":"mački","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"n","osnova2":"zin","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"n","osnova2":"žan","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"n","osnova2":"žno","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"n","osnova2":"žnost","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"obil","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"obil","osnova2":"žavati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"obil","osnova2":"žiti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"ob","osnova2":"d","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"ob","osnova2":"kt","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"ob","osnova2":"ktni","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"ob","osnova2":"siti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"oblikoslovl","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"obl","osnova2":"tnica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"obl","osnova2":"tnički","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"obrazovan","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"oc","osnova2":"na","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"odgojitel","osnova2":"v","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"od","osnova2":"ća","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"od","osnova2":"kivati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"od","osnova2":"knuti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"od","osnova2":"l","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"od","osnova2":"nuti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"održavan","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"oduševl","osnova2":"n","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"oduševl","osnova2":"no","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"oduševl","osnova2":"nost","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"oduziman","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"ogr","osnova2":"v","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"omil","osnova2":"n","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"omil","osnova2":"no","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"omil","osnova2":"nost","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"om","osnova2":"r","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"opkoračen","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"orgul","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"oruž","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"osiguran","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"os","osnova2":"čki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"os","osnova2":"ćaj","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"os","osnova2":"ćajan","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"os","osnova2":"ćajno","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"os","osnova2":"ćajnost","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"os","osnova2":"ćati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"os","osnova2":"t","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"os","osnova2":"tilo","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"os","osnova2":"tiljiv","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"os","osnova2":"titi","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"os","osnova2":"tljivo","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"os","osnova2":"tljivost","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"osmom","osnova2":"sečni","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"ovd","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"ozl","osnova2":"da","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"pamćen","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"pas","osnova2":"menik","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"pečen","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"pel","osnova2":"ški","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"per","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"peteros","osnova2":"d","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"petom","osnova2":"sečni","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"pitan","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"p","osnova2":"na","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"p","osnova2":"sma","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"p","osnova2":"smarica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"p","osnova2":"snički","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"p","osnova2":"snik","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"p","osnova2":"snikinja","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"p","osnova2":"snikinjin","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"p","osnova2":"snikov","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"p","osnova2":"šački","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"p","osnova2":"šak","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"p","osnova2":"šakinja","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"p","osnova2":"šakinjin","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"p","osnova2":"šakov","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"p","osnova2":"ščanik","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"p","osnova2":"šice","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"p","osnova2":"vač","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"p","osnova2":"vačev","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"p","osnova2":"vačica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"p","osnova2":"vačičin","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"p","osnova2":"vački","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"p","osnova2":"vati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"plav","osnova2":"ti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"pob","osnova2":"da","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"podnož","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"područ","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"poglavl","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"po","osnova2":"dinac","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"po","osnova2":"dini","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"po","osnova2":"sti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"polet","osnova2":"ti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"pol","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"ponašan","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"poned","osnova2":"ljak","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"poosobl","osnova2":"n","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"pos","osnova2":"ćivati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"pos","osnova2":"t","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"pos","osnova2":"titi","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"poslovan","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"posl","osnova2":"dica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"posl","osnova2":"dnji","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"posto","osnova2":"ći","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"pošten","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"poštovan","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"potkrovl","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"pov","osnova2":"ren","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"pov","osnova2":"rljiv","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"pov","osnova2":"rljivo","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"pov","osnova2":"rljivost","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"pov","osnova2":"stica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"pov","osnova2":"tarac","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"prad","osnova2":"d","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"prad","osnova2":"dov","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"predavan","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"preds","osnova2":"dati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"preds","osnova2":"davati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"preds","osnova2":"dnica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"preds","osnova2":"dničin","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"preds","osnova2":"dnički","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"preds","osnova2":"dnik","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"preds","osnova2":"dnikov","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"preds","osnova2":"dnikovati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"predsobl","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"predvor","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"prem","osnova2":"stiti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"prem","osnova2":"štati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"prep","osnova2":"v","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"preuziman","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"prevoditel","osnova2":"v","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"pričan","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"prid","osnova2":"v","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"prid","osnova2":"vni","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"prijatel","osnova2":"v","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"prim","osnova2":"ćivati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"prim","osnova2":"r","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"prim","osnova2":"ren","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"prim","osnova2":"reno","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"prim","osnova2":"renost","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"prim","osnova2":"rice","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"primor","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"prip","osnova2":"v","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"pripov","osnova2":"dač","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"pripov","osnova2":"dačev","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"pripov","osnova2":"dačica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"pripov","osnova2":"dačičin","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"prizeml","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"priznan","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"pročel","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"pro","osnova2":"kcija","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"pro","osnova2":"kt","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"pro","osnova2":"ktil","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"pro","osnova2":"ktor","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"prol","osnova2":"će","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"prol","osnova2":"tni","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"prom","osnova2":"na","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"prom","osnova2":"njiv","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"prom","osnova2":"njivo","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"prom","osnova2":"njivost","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"propov","osnova2":"daona","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"propov","osnova2":"daonica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"pros","osnova2":"čan","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"pros","osnova2":"čno","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"pros","osnova2":"čnost","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"prov","osnova2":"ravati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"prov","osnova2":"riti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"putovan","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"putovan","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"ran","osnova2":"nica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"ran","osnova2":"ničin","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"ran","osnova2":"nički","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"ran","osnova2":"nik","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"ran","osnova2":"nikov","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"raskriž","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"ravnatel","osnova2":"v","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"razdobl","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"razum","osnova2":"ti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"r","osnova2":"čnik","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"r","osnova2":"šavati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"r","osnova2":"šen","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"roditel","osnova2":"v","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"rođen","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"rolan","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"rubl","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"samouv","osnova2":"ren","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"samouv","osnova2":"reno","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"samouv","osnova2":"renost","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"sara","osnova2":"vski","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"sav","osnova2":"t","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"sedmom","osnova2":"sečni","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"siv","osnova2":"ti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"s","osnova2":"cište","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"s","osnova2":"ćati se","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"s","osnova2":"ći","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"s","osnova2":"dalica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"s","osnova2":"dalo","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"s","osnova2":"dati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"s","osnova2":"diti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"s","osnova2":"dnica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"s","osnova2":"kira","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"s","osnova2":"me","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"s","osnova2":"menik","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"s","osnova2":"menka","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"s","osnova2":"na","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"s","osnova2":"sti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"s","osnova2":"titi se","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"s","osnova2":"ver","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"s","osnova2":"verni","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"s","osnova2":"veroistočni","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"s","osnova2":"veroistok","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"s","osnova2":"verozapad","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"s","osnova2":"verozapadni","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"skladatel","osnova2":"v","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"sklopovl","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"slatkor","osnova2":"čiv","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"slatkor","osnova2":"čivo","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"slatkor","osnova2":"čivost","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"slavl","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"sl","osnova2":"deći","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"sm","osnova2":"r","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"sm","osnova2":"ran","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"sm","osnova2":"rno","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"sm","osnova2":"rnost","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"sm","osnova2":"ti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"smršav","osnova2":"ti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"sn","osnova2":"gović","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"sn","osnova2":"žan","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"stan","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"stol","osnova2":"će","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"stvaran","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"sub","osnova2":"kt","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"sub","osnova2":"ktni","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"sučel","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"sud","osnova2":"lovati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"sus","osnova2":"d","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"sus","osnova2":"da","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"sus","osnova2":"din","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"sus","osnova2":"dni","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"sus","osnova2":"dov","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"sus","osnova2":"dski","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"sus","osnova2":"dstvo","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"susn","osnova2":"žica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"sut","osnova2":"ški","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"sve","osnova2":"dno","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"svid","osnova2":"ti se","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"svin","osnova2":"ći","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"svin","osnova2":"tina","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"sv","osnova2":"ćica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"sv","osnova2":"sno","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"sv","osnova2":"snost","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"sv","osnova2":"stan","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"sv","osnova2":"tiljka","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"sv","osnova2":"tionik","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"sv","osnova2":"tlo","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"sv","osnova2":"tlost","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"sv","osnova2":"tski","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"sv","osnova2":"ž","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"sv","osnova2":"že","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"sv","osnova2":"žina","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"šestom","osnova2":"sečni","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"škljocan","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"školovan","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"šljapkan","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"šted","osnova2":"ti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"šum","osnova2":"ti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"šupl","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"šut","osnova2":"ti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"t","osnova2":"dan","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"t","osnova2":"lesni","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"t","osnova2":"me","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"t","osnova2":"rati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"t","osnova2":"stenina","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"tlakom","osnova2":"r","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"toplom","osnova2":"r","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"tra","osnova2":"kt","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"trešn","osnova2":"v","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"tro","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"trom","osnova2":"sečni","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"tror","osnova2":"čan","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"tros","osnova2":"d","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"trot","osnova2":"dni","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"tun","osnova2":"vina","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"učen","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"učitel","osnova2":"v","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"udal","osnova2":"n","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"udal","osnova2":"no","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"udal","osnova2":"nost","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"ugl","osnova2":"n","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"u","osnova2":"dno","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"ul","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"uman","osnova2":"nica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"uman","osnova2":"nik","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"umirovl","osnova2":"nica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"umirovl","osnova2":"ničin","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"umirovl","osnova2":"nik","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"um","osnova2":"ren","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"um","osnova2":"reno","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"um","osnova2":"renost","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"um","osnova2":"sto","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"um","osnova2":"tnica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"um","osnova2":"tničin","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"um","osnova2":"tnik","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"um","osnova2":"tnost","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"usp","osnova2":"h","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"usp","osnova2":"šan","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"usp","osnova2":"ti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"utemel","osnova2":"n","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"ut","osnova2":"caj","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"ut","osnova2":"cajan","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"ut","osnova2":"cati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"uv","osnova2":"t","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"vesel","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"vid","osnova2":"ti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"vis","osnova2":"ti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"više","osnova2":"zičan","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"višem","osnova2":"sečni","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"višet","osnova2":"dni","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"v","osnova2":"čnost","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"v","osnova2":"nčan","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"v","osnova2":"nčati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"v","osnova2":"ra","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"v","osnova2":"rnica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"v","osnova2":"rničin","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"v","osnova2":"rnik","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"v","osnova2":"rojatan","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"v","osnova2":"rojatno","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"v","osnova2":"rojatnost","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"v","osnova2":"ronauk","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"v","osnova2":"roučitelj","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"v","osnova2":"roučitel","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"v","osnova2":"roučiteljica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"v","osnova2":"roučiteljičin","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"v","osnova2":"roučiteljski","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"v","osnova2":"rovati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"v","osnova2":"rski","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"v","osnova2":"snik","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"v","osnova2":"šala","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"v","osnova2":"šalica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"v","osnova2":"štica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"v","osnova2":"ština","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"v","osnova2":"tar","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"v","osnova2":"trovit","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"v","osnova2":"trovito","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"v","osnova2":"verica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"v","osnova2":"žba","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"v","osnova2":"žbati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"v","osnova2":"žbenica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"v","osnova2":"žbeničin","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"v","osnova2":"žbenički","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"v","osnova2":"žbenik","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"v","osnova2":"žbenikov","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"vodom","osnova2":"r","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"vol","osnova2":"ti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"vrhn","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"vrt","osnova2":"ti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"zaglavl","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"zaht","osnova2":"v","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"za","osnova2":"čati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"za","osnova2":"dnica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"za","osnova2":"dnički","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"za","osnova2":"dno","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"zal","osnova2":"v","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"zaljubl","osnova2":"n","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"zaljubl","osnova2":"no","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"zaljubl","osnova2":"nost","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"zam","osnova2":"na","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"zam","osnova2":"nica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"zam","osnova2":"ničin","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"zam","osnova2":"nični","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"zam","osnova2":"nik","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"zam","osnova2":"nikov","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"zaniman","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"zap","osnova2":"vati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"zavid","osnova2":"ti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"zav","osnova2":"sa","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"zbrajan","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"zbun","osnova2":"n","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"zbun","osnova2":"no","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"zbun","osnova2":"nost","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"zd","osnova2":"la","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"zdravl","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"zelen","osnova2":"ti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"zel","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"z","osnova2":"nica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"zlostavljan","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"znan","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"zv","osnova2":"zdača","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"zv","osnova2":"zdica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"žel","osnova2":"ti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"žel","osnova2":"znica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"žel","osnova2":"zo","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"živ","osnova2":"ti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"žrtvovan","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"žud","osnova2":"ti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"ije/je","correctAnswer":["je","ije"],"osnova":"žut","osnova2":"ti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
], 
 
 p2 = [
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"﻿admirali","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"afri","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"aktivisti","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"aktivisti","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"alkoholi","osnova2":"ar","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"alkoholi","osnova2":"arev","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"alkoholi","osnova2":"arka","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"alkoholi","osnova2":"arkin","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"alkoholi","osnova2":"arov","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"alkoholi","osnova2":"arski","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"alpinisti","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"alpinisti","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"ameri","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"analiti","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"anglisti","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"anglisti","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"antialkoholi","osnova2":"ar","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"antialkoholi","osnova2":"arev","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"antialkoholi","osnova2":"arka","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"antialkoholi","osnova2":"arkin","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"antialkoholi","osnova2":"arov","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"antialkoholi","osnova2":"arski","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"arhitekti","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"arhivisti","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"arhivisti","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"automehani","osnova2":"ar","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"automehani","osnova2":"arev","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"automehani","osnova2":"arka","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"automehani","osnova2":"arkin","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"automehani","osnova2":"arov","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"automehani","osnova2":"arski","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"autor","osnova2":"ić-","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"autori","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"avion","osnova2":"ić-","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"babi","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"baca","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"baca","osnova2":"ev","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"baca","osnova2":"ica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"baca","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"baca","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"ba","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"ba","osnova2":"va","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"ba","osnova2":"var","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"ba","osnova2":"varev","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"ba","osnova2":"varica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"ba","osnova2":"vari","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"ba","osnova2":"varov","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"ba","osnova2":"varski","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"ba","osnova2":"vica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"balkon","osnova2":"ić-","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"balon","osnova2":"ić-","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"bani","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"banjolu","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"baruni","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"bazen","osnova2":"ić-","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"be","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"beletristi","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"benkova","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"beskona","osnova2":"an","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"beskona","osnova2":"no","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"beskona","osnova2":"nost","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"biciklisti","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"biciklisti","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"bilježni","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"bilježni","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"bjelogori","osnova2":"ni","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"blizana","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"blizan","osnova2":"ev","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"bogataši","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"bojni","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"bojni","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"boksa","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"boksa","osnova2":"ica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"boksa","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"boksa","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"bolni","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"bra","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"bra","osnova2":"ni","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"branitelji","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"brbljav","osnova2":"ev","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"brbljavi","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"br","osnova2":"ić-","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"br","osnova2":"ina","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"bren","osnova2":"ati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"brisa","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"broja","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"broj","osnova2":"anik","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"bron","osnova2":"an","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"bron","osnova2":"ani","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"bubnjari","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"bu","osnova2":"an","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"bu","osnova2":"ati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"bu","osnova2":"ati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"bu","osnova2":"iti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"budali","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"bukovi","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"busova","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"cari","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"ci","osnova2":"ati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"cimeri","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"cin","osnova2":"ani","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"cjev","osnova2":"ica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"crikveni","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"crnogori","osnova2":"ni","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"crtan","osnova2":"ica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"crti","osnova2":"ni","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"curi","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"cvjeta","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"cvr","osnova2":"ak","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"cvr","osnova2":"ati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"adski","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"aj","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"ak","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"akove","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"amac","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"apljinski","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"arapa","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"aroban","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"arobnica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"arobni","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"arobnja","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"arobnjak","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"arobnjakov","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"as","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"asnica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"asni","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"asni","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"asnik","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"asnikov","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"asopis","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"ast","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"aša","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"avao","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"e","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"egrtaljka","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"ekanje","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"ekaona","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"ekaonica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"ekati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"ekić-","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"ekrk","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"elik","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"elo","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"empres","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"est","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"estica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"esti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"estit","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"estitati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"estitka","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"estito","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"estitost","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"esto","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"estoća-","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"ešalj","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"eški","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"ešljanje","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"ešljaona","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"ešljaonica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"ešljati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"ešnjak","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"etiri","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"etiristo","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"etiristoti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"etka","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"etkati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"etkica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"etrdeset","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"etrdesetak","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"etrdesetero","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"etrdeseti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"etrdesetogodišnjak","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"etrdesetogodišnjakinja","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"etrdesetogodišnji","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"etrdesetogodišnjica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"etrdesetorica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"etrnaest","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"etrnaestero","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"etrnaesti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"etveri","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"etvero","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"etverodijelan","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"etverodimenzijski","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"etverodimenzionalni","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"etverogodišnjak","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"etverogodišnjakinja","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"etverogodišnji","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"etverokatni","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"etverokatnica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"etverokratnik","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"etverokut","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"etveromjese","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"etveroredan","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"etverorje","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"etverosjed","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"etverosoban","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"etverostruk","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"etvorica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"etvorka","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"etvrt","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"etvrtak","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"etvrtaš","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"etvrtašica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"etvrti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"etvrtica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"etvrtina","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"etvrtinka","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"eznuti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"igra","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"iji","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"ijigod","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"ikaški","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"ileanski","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"im","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"im","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"imbenik","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"inele","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"initi","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"initi se","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"injenica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"ip","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"ist","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"ista","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"ista","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"ista","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"ista","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"ista","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"istiona","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"istionica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"istiti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"ita","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"itanka","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"itaona","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"itaonica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"itati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"itav","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"itlu","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"izma","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"lan","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"lanak","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"lanica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"lani","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"lanov","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"lanski","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"okolada","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"ovjek","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"u","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"u","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"uditi se","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"udo","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"uti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"uvati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"vor","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"vor","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"vrst","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"vrsto","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"ćelav","osnova2":"ev-","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"ćevap","osnova2":"ić-","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"ćirili","osnova2":"ni-","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"dalekopisa","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"daltonisti","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"daš","osnova2":"ica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"de","osnova2":"ko","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"de","osnova2":"kov","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"delni","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"desetni","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"desetni","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"desetomjese","osnova2":"ni","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"dešnja","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"devetomjese","osnova2":"ni","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"di","osnova2":"iti se","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"dijeteti","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"dinami","osnova2":"an","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"direktori","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"dizajneri","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"dje","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"dje","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"dje","osnova2":"ak","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"dje","osnova2":"akov","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"dje","osnova2":"ji","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"djevi","osnova2":"anski","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"djevi","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"djevoja","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"djevoj","osnova2":"ica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"djevoj","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"djevoj","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"dla","osnova2":"ica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"do","osnova2":"asnica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"do","osnova2":"asni","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"do","osnova2":"asni","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"do","osnova2":"asnik","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"do","osnova2":"asnikov","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"do","osnova2":"im","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"doktori","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"domaći","osnova2":"in-","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"donjomiholja","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"doru","osnova2":"ak","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"doru","osnova2":"kovati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"dra","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"druga","osnova2":"iji","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"drugaši","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"druk","osnova2":"iji","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"dubrova","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"dudaši","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"duga","osnova2":"ak","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"dugooto","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"duši","osnova2":"ni","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"dvojezi","osnova2":"an","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"dvoli","osnova2":"an","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"dvoli","osnova2":"no","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"dvoli","osnova2":"nost","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"dvomjese","osnova2":"ni","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"dvorje","osnova2":"an","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"dvoto","osnova2":"ka","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"đakova","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"đavol","osnova2":"ev","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"đavol","osnova2":"ić-","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"đavol","osnova2":"ićev-","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"đavoli","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"đurđeva","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"egzoti","osnova2":"an","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"fagotisti","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"fagotisti","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"fizi","osnova2":"ar","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"fizi","osnova2":"arka","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"flautisti","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"flautisti","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"frulaši","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"gajdaši","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"garešni","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"generali","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"gimnasti","osnova2":"ar","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"gimnasti","osnova2":"arev","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"gimnasti","osnova2":"arka","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"gimnasti","osnova2":"arkin","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"gimnasti","osnova2":"arov","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"gimnasti","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"gitaristi","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"gitaristi","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"gla","osnova2":"alo","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"gla","osnova2":"ati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"glagolji","osnova2":"ni","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"gledatelji","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"gležnja","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"gluma","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"glum","osnova2":"ev","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"glumi","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"gra","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"grada","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"gradona","osnova2":"elnik","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"gramati","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"gr","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"grija","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"guš","osnova2":"etina","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"guš","osnova2":"ji","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"harfisti","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"harfisti","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"harmonikaši","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"hercegova","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"hla","osnova2":"e","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"hr","osnova2":"ak","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"hrvata","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"hu","osnova2":"ati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"hu","osnova2":"iti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"humoristi","osnova2":"an","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"i","osnova2":"iji","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"idealisti","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"idealisti","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"igra","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"igra","osnova2":"ev","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"igra","osnova2":"ica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"igra","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"igra","osnova2":"ka","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"igra","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"ilo","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"iluzionisti","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"imeni","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"ina","osnova2":"e","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"informati","osnova2":"ar","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"informati","osnova2":"arev","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"informati","osnova2":"arka","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"informati","osnova2":"arov","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"informati","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"ira","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"iseljeni","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"isklju","osnova2":"iti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"isklju","osnova2":"ivo","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"ispri","osnova2":"ati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"ispri","osnova2":"avati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"ispri","osnova2":"nica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"isto","osnova2":"ni","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"ivan","osnova2":"ica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"ivane","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"izborni","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"izdaji","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"izdajni","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"izdajni","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"ja","osnova2":"anje","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"ja","osnova2":"ati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"ja","osnova2":"ina","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"jaja","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"jamaja","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"janjeva","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"jastu","osnova2":"nica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"javnobilježni","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"je","osnova2":"ati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"jedini","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"jedna","osnova2":"enje","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"jednojezi","osnova2":"an","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"jednomjese","osnova2":"ni","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"jednorje","osnova2":"an","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"jezi","osnova2":"ac","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"jezi","osnova2":"ak","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"jezi","osnova2":"ast","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"jezi","osnova2":"av","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"jezi","osnova2":"avost","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"jezi","osnova2":"ni","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"ju","osnova2":"er","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"ju","osnova2":"er","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"jugoisto","osnova2":"ni","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"juna","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"južnoafri","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"južnoameri","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"kalja","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"kapetani","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"kapulja","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"karlova","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"katoli","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"kau","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"kembri","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"kipari","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"kiselja","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"klarinetisti","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"klarinetisti","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"klaviristi","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"klaviristi","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"kle","osnova2":"ati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"klju","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"književni","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"knjižni","osnova2":"ar","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"knjižni","osnova2":"arev","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"knjižni","osnova2":"arka","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"knjižni","osnova2":"arkin","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"knjižni","osnova2":"arov","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"knjižni","osnova2":"arski","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"knjižni","osnova2":"arstvo","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"ko","osnova2":"ijaš","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"ko","osnova2":"nica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"kola","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"koli","osnova2":"ina","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"koli","osnova2":"nik","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"komandanti","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"kona","osnova2":"an","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"kona","osnova2":"no","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"kona","osnova2":"nost","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"konobari","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"kontrabasisti","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"kontrabasisti","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"kopa","osnova2":"ka","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"koprivni","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"kor","osnova2":"ulanski","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"korisni","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"korisni","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"kornja","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"kota","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"kova","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"kov","osnova2":"eg","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"kovr","osnova2":"av","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"kovr","osnova2":"avost","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"kozmeti","osnova2":"ar","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"kozmeti","osnova2":"arev","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"kozmeti","osnova2":"arka","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"kozmeti","osnova2":"arkin","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"kozmeti","osnova2":"arov","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"kozmeti","osnova2":"arski","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"kozmeti","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"kr","osnova2":"ati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"kr","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"križeva","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"krma","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"kroja","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"kroja","osnova2":"ev","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"kroja","osnova2":"ica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"kroja","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"kroja","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"ksilofonisti","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"kućani","osnova2":"in-","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"kuhari","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"kum","osnova2":"e","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"kupaoni","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"kup","osnova2":"ev","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"kvadrati","osnova2":"an","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"ladi","osnova2":"ar","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"lan","osnova2":"ić-","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"latini","osnova2":"ni","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"lavi","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"li","osnova2":"inka","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"li","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"lije","osnova2":"iti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"lije","osnova2":"nica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"lije","osnova2":"ni","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"lije","osnova2":"ni","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"lije","osnova2":"nik","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"lije","osnova2":"nikov","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"lijeri","osnova2":"ar","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"lijeri","osnova2":"arev","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"lijeri","osnova2":"arka","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"lijeri","osnova2":"arov","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"lijeri","osnova2":"arski","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"lingvisti","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"lingvisti","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"lisi","osnova2":"ji","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"lon","osnova2":"ić-","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"lopo","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"lova","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"lov","osnova2":"ev","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"ljekarni","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"ljekarni","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"ljubi","osnova2":"ast","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"ljubim","osnova2":"ev","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"ljubimi","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"ljulja","osnova2":"ka","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"ma","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"ma","osnova2":"ak","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"ma","osnova2":"e","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"ma","osnova2":"ić-","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"ma","osnova2":"ka","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"ma","osnova2":"kica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"mađioni","osnova2":"ar","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"mađioni","osnova2":"arev","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"mađioni","osnova2":"arka","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"mađioni","osnova2":"arkin","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"mađioni","osnova2":"arov","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"mađioni","osnova2":"arski","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"maj","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"maj","osnova2":"inski","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"majori","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"mandolinisti","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"mandolinisti","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"marijabistri","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"masla","osnova2":"ak","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"matemati","osnova2":"ar","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"matemati","osnova2":"arev","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"matemati","osnova2":"arka","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"matemati","osnova2":"arkin","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"matemati","osnova2":"arov","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"matemati","osnova2":"arski","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"materijalisti","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"materijalisti","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"maturanti","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"mehani","osnova2":"ar","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"mehani","osnova2":"arev","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"mehani","osnova2":"arka","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"mehani","osnova2":"arkin","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"mehani","osnova2":"arov","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"mehani","osnova2":"arski","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"meksi","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"menadžeri","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"mesari","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"minira","osnova2":"unalo","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"ministri","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"minobaca","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"mjenja","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"mjenja","osnova2":"ica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"mjenja","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"mjenja","osnova2":"nica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"mjese","osnova2":"ina","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"mjese","osnova2":"no","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"mladun","osnova2":"e","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"mlije","osnova2":"ni","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"moma","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"mom","osnova2":"ad","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"mornari","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"mornari","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"mozambi","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"mu","osnova2":"iti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"muškar","osnova2":"ev","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"na","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"nadnaredni","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"nadnaredni","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"nanora","osnova2":"unalo","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"nao","osnova2":"ale","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"naran","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"naran","osnova2":"ast","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"naredni","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"naredni","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"naru","osnova2":"iti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"naru","osnova2":"ivati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"naslonja","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"nastavni","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"nastavni","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"naši","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"natika","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"natjecatelji","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"natje","osnova2":"aj","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"natporu","osnova2":"nica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"natporu","osnova2":"ni","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"natporu","osnova2":"ni","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"natporu","osnova2":"nik","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"natporu","osnova2":"nikov","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"nau","osnova2":"iti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"nave","osnova2":"er","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"navija","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"navija","osnova2":"ev","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"navija","osnova2":"ica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"navija","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"navija","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"ne","osnova2":"iji","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"neodlu","osnova2":"an","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"neodlu","osnova2":"no","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"neodlu","osnova2":"nost","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"nepliva","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"nepliva","osnova2":"ev","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"nepliva","osnova2":"ica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"nepliva","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"nepuša","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"nepuša","osnova2":"ev","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"nepuša","osnova2":"ica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"nepuša","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"nepuša","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"nevodi","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"nevoza","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"nevoza","osnova2":"ev","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"nevoza","osnova2":"ica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"nevoza","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"nevoza","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"ni","osnova2":"iji","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"nogometaši","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"nosa","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"nov","osnova2":"anica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"nov","osnova2":"anik","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"novorođen","osnova2":"e","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"njema","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"obi","osnova2":"an","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"obi","osnova2":"no","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"obla","osnova2":"an","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"obla","osnova2":"iti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"obla","osnova2":"iti se","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"obla","osnova2":"ni","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"obla","osnova2":"no","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"obljetni","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"oboisti","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"oboisti","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"obrtni","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"obrtni","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"o","osnova2":"ekivati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"o","osnova2":"ev","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"o","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"o","osnova2":"inski","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"o","osnova2":"it","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"o","osnova2":"ito","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"o","osnova2":"uh","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"o","osnova2":"uhov","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"odašilja","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"odbojkaši","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"odgojitelji","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"odli","osnova2":"an","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"odli","osnova2":"no","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"odlu","osnova2":"an","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"odlu","osnova2":"iti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"odlu","osnova2":"ivati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"odlu","osnova2":"no","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"odlu","osnova2":"nost","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"ogrta","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"okulisti","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"opkora","osnova2":"enje","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"optimisti","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"orguljaši","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"osigura","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"osje","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"osmomjese","osnova2":"ni","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"otklju","osnova2":"ati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"otklju","osnova2":"avati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"oto","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"otvara","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"ozna","osnova2":"avati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"ozna","osnova2":"iti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"pacijenti","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"pa","osnova2":"e","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"pa","osnova2":"etina","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"pa","osnova2":"ji","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"pakra","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"pala","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"pala","osnova2":"inka","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"pal","osnova2":"ić-","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"papu","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"partneri","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"pastiri","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"pau","osnova2":"ica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"pau","osnova2":"ina","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"p","osnova2":"ela","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"pe","osnova2":"enje","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"pedagogi","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"pekari","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"pesimisti","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"petomjese","osnova2":"ni","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"pijanisti","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"pijanisti","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"pisa","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"piš","osnova2":"ev","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"pjesni","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"pješa","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"pješ","osnova2":"anik","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"pjeva","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"pjeva","osnova2":"ev","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"pjeva","osnova2":"ica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"pjeva","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"pjeva","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"pla","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"pla","osnova2":"ljiv","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"pla","osnova2":"ljivo","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"pla","osnova2":"ljivost","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"plamenja","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"plesa","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"plesa","osnova2":"ev","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"plesa","osnova2":"ica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"plesa","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"plesa","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"pliva","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"pliva","osnova2":"ev","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"pliva","osnova2":"ica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"pliva","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"pliva","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"plo","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"plo","osnova2":"anski","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"plo","osnova2":"nik","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"plja","osnova2":"ka","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"pljuva","osnova2":"ka","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"po","osnova2":"ešljati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"po","osnova2":"etak","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"po","osnova2":"eti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"po","osnova2":"etnica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"po","osnova2":"injati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"podru","osnova2":"je","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"podru","osnova2":"ni","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"poja","osnova2":"alo","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"pokaziva","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"pokriva","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"policaj","osnova2":"ev","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"politi","osnova2":"ar","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"politi","osnova2":"arev","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"politi","osnova2":"arka","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"politi","osnova2":"arkin","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"politi","osnova2":"arov","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"politi","osnova2":"arski","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"politi","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"politi","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"polusloženi","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"polji","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"poljoprivredni","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"poljoprivredni","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"pore","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"poru","osnova2":"nica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"poru","osnova2":"ni","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"poru","osnova2":"ni","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"poru","osnova2":"nik","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"poru","osnova2":"nikov","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"poštari","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"potporu","osnova2":"nica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"potporu","osnova2":"ni","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"potporu","osnova2":"ni","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"potporu","osnova2":"nik","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"potporu","osnova2":"nikov","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"potpukovni","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"potpukovni","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"poznani","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"pozorni","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"pozorni","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"pr","osnova2":"anjski","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"pre","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"predsjedni","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"predsjedni","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"predstavni","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"predstavni","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"prekida","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"presko","osnova2":"iti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"prevoditelji","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"pri","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"pri","osnova2":"anje","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"pri","osnova2":"ati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"pri","osnova2":"ati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"pri","osnova2":"est","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"prigušiva","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"prijatelji","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"priklju","osnova2":"iti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"priklju","osnova2":"ivati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"pripovjeda","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"pripovjeda","osnova2":"ev","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"pripovjeda","osnova2":"ica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"pripovjeda","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"pristupa","osnova2":"an","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"pristupa","osnova2":"no","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"pristupa","osnova2":"nost","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"privla","osnova2":"an","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"privla","osnova2":"no","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"privla","osnova2":"nost","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"pro","osnova2":"elje","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"pro","osnova2":"išćiva","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"pro","osnova2":"itati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"prodava","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"prodava","osnova2":"ev","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"prodava","osnova2":"ica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"prodava","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"prodava","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"profesori","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"proizvođa","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"proizvođa","osnova2":"ica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"proizvođa","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"prolazni","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"prolazni","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"prometni","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"prometni","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"prora","osnova2":"un","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"prosje","osnova2":"an","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"prosje","osnova2":"no","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"prosje","osnova2":"nost","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"prostira","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"protivni","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"protivni","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"prou","osnova2":"avati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"prou","osnova2":"iti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"prva","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"prvaši","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"pti","osnova2":"ica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"pu","osnova2":"iški","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"pukovni","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"pukovni","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"punja","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"puša","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"puša","osnova2":"ev","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"puša","osnova2":"ica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"puša","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"puša","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"putni","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"putni","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"ra","osnova2":"ić-","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"ra","osnova2":"ji","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"ra","osnova2":"un","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"ra","osnova2":"unalni","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"ra","osnova2":"unalo","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"ra","osnova2":"unalstvo","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"ra","osnova2":"unati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"radni","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"radni","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"raj","osnova2":"ica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"ranjeni","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"ranjeni","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"rasplinja","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"raspršiva","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"raš","osnova2":"lamba","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"ratni","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"ratni","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"ravnatelji","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"razli","osnova2":"it","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"razli","osnova2":"ito","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"razli","osnova2":"itost","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"razvodni","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"razvodni","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"re","osnova2":"enica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"redovni","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"redovni","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"ribari","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"rije","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"rije","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"rije","osnova2":"ni","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"rimokatoli","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"rje","osnova2":"nik","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"ro","osnova2":"nica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"ro","osnova2":"ni","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"ro","osnova2":"ni","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"ro","osnova2":"nik","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"ro","osnova2":"nikov","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"roditelji","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"rođa","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"rombi","osnova2":"an","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"ronila","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"ronio","osnova2":"ev","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"ronitelji","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"ru","osnova2":"ak","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"ru","osnova2":"ati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"ru","osnova2":"e","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"ru","osnova2":"nik","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"rukometaši","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"rup","osnova2":"ić-","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"ruži","osnova2":"ast","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"ruži","osnova2":"asto","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"saksofonisti","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"saksofonisti","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"satni","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"satni","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"savija","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"sebi","osnova2":"an","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"sebi","osnova2":"no","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"sebi","osnova2":"nost","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"sedmomjese","osnova2":"ni","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"selja","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"sendvi","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"sestri","osnova2":"na","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"sestri","osnova2":"nin","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"sije","osnova2":"anj","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"simpati","osnova2":"an","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"simpati","osnova2":"no","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"sisa","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"sjeveroisto","osnova2":"ni","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"skijaši","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"skladatelji","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"sko","osnova2":"iti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"skupni","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"slasti","osnova2":"arna","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"slasti","osnova2":"arnica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"slatkorje","osnova2":"iv","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"slatkorje","osnova2":"ivo","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"slatkorje","osnova2":"ivost","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"sli","osnova2":"an","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"sli","osnova2":"no","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"sli","osnova2":"nost","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"slikari","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"slova","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"slu","osnova2":"aj","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"slu","osnova2":"ajan","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"slu","osnova2":"ajno","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"slu","osnova2":"ajnost","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"smo","osnova2":"nica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"sobari","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"so","osnova2":"an","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"so","osnova2":"no","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"so","osnova2":"nost","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"sopilaši","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"spi","osnova2":"anski","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"spisatelji","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"sportaši","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"sprema","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"sprema","osnova2":"ev","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"sprema","osnova2":"ica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"sprema","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"sprema","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"srda","osnova2":"an","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"srda","osnova2":"no","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"srda","osnova2":"nost","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"stan","osnova2":"ić-","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"stanovni","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"stara","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"star","osnova2":"ev","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"stari","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"stepeni","osnova2":"ast","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"sto","osnova2":"ar","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"sto","osnova2":"arev","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"sto","osnova2":"arica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"sto","osnova2":"ari","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"sto","osnova2":"arov","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"sto","osnova2":"arski","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"sto","osnova2":"arstvo","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"stomatologi","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"strana","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"stran","osnova2":"ev","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"stri","osnova2":"ev","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"strijel","osnova2":"ev","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"stru","osnova2":"an","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"stru","osnova2":"no","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"stru","osnova2":"nost","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"stru","osnova2":"njak","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"stru","osnova2":"njakinja","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"strunja","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"studenti","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"suboti","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"su","osnova2":"elje","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"suda","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"sud","osnova2":"ev","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"sudioni","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"sun","osnova2":"an","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"sun","osnova2":"ano","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"sun","osnova2":"ati se","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"sure","osnova2":"enica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"suvoza","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"suvoza","osnova2":"ev","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"suvoza","osnova2":"ica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"suvoza","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"suvoza","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"sva","osnova2":"iji","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"sve","osnova2":"an","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"sve","osnova2":"ano","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"sve","osnova2":"anost","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"sveta","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"svet","osnova2":"ev","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"sveti","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"sveu","osnova2":"ilište","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"svira","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"svira","osnova2":"ev","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"svira","osnova2":"ica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"svira","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"šahisti","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"šestomjese","osnova2":"ni","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"šumari","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"tajni","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"tajni","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"taksisti","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"tamburaši","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"te","osnova2":"aj","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"tehni","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"tenisa","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"tenisa","osnova2":"ev","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"tenisa","osnova2":"ica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"tenisa","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"tenisa","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"timpanisti","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"to","osnova2":"an","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"to","osnova2":"iti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"to","osnova2":"ka","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"to","osnova2":"kica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"to","osnova2":"no","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"to","osnova2":"nost","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"tra","osnova2":"nica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"tratin","osnova2":"ica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"travni","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"tr","osnova2":"ati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"trećaši","osnova2":"in-","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"treneri","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"trenuta","osnova2":"an","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"trenuta","osnova2":"no","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"trgova","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"trgov","osnova2":"ev","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"trombonisti","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"tromjese","osnova2":"ni","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"trorje","osnova2":"an","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"troto","osnova2":"ka","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"truba","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"truba","osnova2":"ev","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"truba","osnova2":"ica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"truba","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"truba","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"tubisti","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"tu","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"tu","osnova2":"ak","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"tu","osnova2":"njava","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"turisti","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"turisti","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"u","osnova2":".","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"u","osnova2":"enica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"u","osnova2":"eni","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"u","osnova2":"eni","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"u","osnova2":"enik","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"u","osnova2":"enikov","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"u","osnova2":"enje","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"u","osnova2":"estalost","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"u","osnova2":"initi","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"u","osnova2":"iona","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"u","osnova2":"ionica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"u","osnova2":"itelj","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"u","osnova2":"iteljev","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"u","osnova2":"iteljica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"u","osnova2":"itelji","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"u","osnova2":"iteljski","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"u","osnova2":"iti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"uklju","osnova2":"iti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"uklju","osnova2":"ivati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"umirovljeni","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"umjetni","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"unato","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"uo","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"upalja","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"upravlja","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"uređiva","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"usisava","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"uskli","osnova2":"ni","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"uskli","osnova2":"nik","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"uspinja","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"vadi","osnova2":"ep","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"valpova","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"valj","osnova2":"ić-","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"vari","osnova2":"ela","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"vaterpolisti","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"vaterpolisti","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"vatrogaš","osnova2":"ev","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"ve","osnova2":"er","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"ve","osnova2":"era","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"ve","osnova2":"eras","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"ve","osnova2":"erati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"ve","osnova2":"ernji","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"vegetarijan","osnova2":"ev","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"vele","osnova2":"asni","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"veli","osnova2":"ina","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"velikogori","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"velolu","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"velja","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"vesla","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"vesla","osnova2":"ev","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"vesla","osnova2":"ica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"vesla","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"vesla","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"vezni","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"viceadmirali","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"vinkova","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"violinisti","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"violinisti","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"violisti","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"violisti","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"violon","osnova2":"elist","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"violon","osnova2":"elistica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"violon","osnova2":"elisti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"violon","osnova2":"elisti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"violon","osnova2":"elistov","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"violon","osnova2":"elo","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"viroviti","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"višejezi","osnova2":"an","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"višekratni","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"višemjese","osnova2":"ni","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"vje","osnova2":"nost","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"vjen","osnova2":"anje","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"vjen","osnova2":"ati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"vjerni","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"vjerou","osnova2":"itelj","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"vjerou","osnova2":"iteljev","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"vjerou","osnova2":"iteljica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"vjerou","osnova2":"itelji","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"vjerou","osnova2":"iteljski","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"vježbeni","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"vježbeni","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"vladari","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"vlasni","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"vodenja","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"vodi","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"vodi","osnova2":"ev","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"vodi","osnova2":"ica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"vodi","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"vodi","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"vodni","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"vodni","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"vojni","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"voza","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"voza","osnova2":"ev","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"voza","osnova2":"ica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"voza","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"voza","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"vraži","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"vu","osnova2":"ić-","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"zagreba","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"zaje","osnova2":"ati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"zajedni","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"zaklju","osnova2":"ak","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"zaklju","osnova2":"iti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"zamjeni","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"zamjeni","osnova2":"ni","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"zamrziva","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"zapo","osnova2":"eti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"zavi","osnova2":"aj","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"ze","osnova2":"etina","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"ze","osnova2":"ić-","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"ze","osnova2":"ji","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"zidari","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"zlo","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"zna","osnova2":"iti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"zna","osnova2":"ka","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"znan","osnova2":"ev","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"znani","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"zuba","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"zubari","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"zvjezda","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"zvr","osnova2":"ati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"ži","osnova2":"ara","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"žli","osnova2":"ica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"žumbera","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"župani","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
    {"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"﻿auti","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"autorči","osnova2":"-","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"avionči","osnova2":"-","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"balkonči","osnova2":"-","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"balonči","osnova2":"-","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"bazenči","osnova2":"-","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"bezosje","osnova2":"ajan","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"bezosje","osnova2":"ajno","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"bezosje","osnova2":"ajnost","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"bicikli","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"bi","osnova2":"e","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"bjelokoš","osnova2":"anski","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"Boži","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"boži","osnova2":"ni","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"bra","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"bra","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"brati","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"brati","osnova2":"ev","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"brči","osnova2":"-","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"brodi","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"bubnji","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"bu","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"bu","osnova2":"kati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"bu","osnova2":"nuti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"budu","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"budu","osnova2":"nost","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"cvije","osnova2":"e","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"cvje","osnova2":"arna","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"cvje","osnova2":"arnica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"cvjeti","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"čeki","osnova2":"-","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"često","osnova2":"a-","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"elav","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"elavac","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"elavčev-","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"elavost","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"evapči","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"ilim","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"irilica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"irilični-","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"ud","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"uk","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"up","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"urlikati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"urliknuti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"desetlje","osnova2":"e","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"dječači","osnova2":"-","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"dječači","osnova2":"ev-","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"dobro","osnova2":"udan","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"dobro","osnova2":"udno","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"dobro","osnova2":"udnost","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"do","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"doma","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"doma","osnova2":"ica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"doma","osnova2":"ičin-","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"doma","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"doma","osnova2":"inov","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"doma","osnova2":"inski","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"došaš","osnova2":"e","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"drve","osnova2":"e","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"du","osnova2":"an","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"džepi","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"đavolči","osnova2":"-","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"đavolči","osnova2":"ev-","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"ga","osnova2":"e","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"gospi","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"goš","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"gradiš","osnova2":"anski","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"gusto","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"hladno","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"i","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"idu","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"ispe","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"ivani","osnova2":"gradski","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"iza","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"izi","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"izvješ","osnova2":"ivati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"izvu","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"janje","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"jare","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"jari","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"june","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"kafi","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"k","osnova2":"er","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"k","osnova2":"erin","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"k","osnova2":"erinski","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"k","osnova2":"erka","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"k","osnova2":"erkin","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"k","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"kozle","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"kozli","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"križi","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"krš","osnova2":"anin","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"krš","osnova2":"aninov","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"krš","osnova2":"anka","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"krš","osnova2":"ankin","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"krš","osnova2":"anski","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"kruži","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"ku","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"ku","osnova2":"anica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"ku","osnova2":"aničin-","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"ku","osnova2":"ica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"ku","osnova2":"ni","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"kune","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"kuni","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"kuni","osnova2":"evina","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"kvadrati","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"lanči","osnova2":"-","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"lavi","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"lavi","osnova2":"ev","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"le","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"le","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"le","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"listi","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"liš","osnova2":"e","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"lonči","osnova2":"-","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"lovre","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"mači","osnova2":"-","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"ma","osnova2":"eha","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"ma","osnova2":"ehin","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"ma","osnova2":"ehinski","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"ma","osnova2":"uhica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"masno","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"medvjedi","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"miši","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"mladi","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"mladi","osnova2":"ev","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"mladi","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"mo","osnova2":"an","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"mo","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"mo","osnova2":"no","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"mogu","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"mogu","osnova2":"nost","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"na","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"ne","osnova2":"ak","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"ne","osnova2":"akinja","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"ne","osnova2":"akinjin","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"ne","osnova2":"akov","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"nesre","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"no","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"no","osnova2":"ni","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"obi","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"obu","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"obu","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"odje","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"oku","osnova2":"nica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"omogu","osnova2":"avati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"omogu","osnova2":"iti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"omogu","osnova2":"ivati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"op","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"op","osnova2":"ina","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"osje","osnova2":"aj","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"osje","osnova2":"ajan","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"osje","osnova2":"ajno","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"osje","osnova2":"ajnost","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"osje","osnova2":"ati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"oti","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"palči","osnova2":"-","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"pam","osnova2":"enje","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"pe","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"pe","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"pe","osnova2":"nica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"pi","osnova2":"e","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"pile","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"pla","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"pla","osnova2":"ati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"plu","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"po","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"poduze","osnova2":"e","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"polno","osnova2":"ka","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"pomo","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"pomo","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"pono","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"pono","osnova2":"ni","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"posje","osnova2":"ivati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"posti","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"postoje","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"pove","osnova2":"alo","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"povr","osnova2":"e","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"pra","osnova2":"ka","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"predboži","osnova2":"ni","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"prihva","osnova2":"ati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"prije","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"primje","osnova2":"ivati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"pročiš","osnova2":"ivač-","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"pro","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"prolje","osnova2":"e","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"prona","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"prsti","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"pure","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"rači","osnova2":"-","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"ražnji","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"re","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"rupči","osnova2":"-","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"si","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"sino","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"sje","osnova2":"ati se","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"sje","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"sljede","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"sme","osnova2":"e","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"snjegovi","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"spava","osnova2":"ica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"sre","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"srnda","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"srne","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"staja","osnova2":"ica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"stanči","osnova2":"-","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"sti","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"stolje","osnova2":"e","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"suho","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"sve","osnova2":"enik","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"svije","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"svije","osnova2":"njak","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"svinje","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"svje","osnova2":"ica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"svu","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"še","osnova2":"er","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"štapi","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"te","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"teku","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"teku","osnova2":"ica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"teku","osnova2":"ina","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"tele","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"tisu","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"tisu","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"tisu","osnova2":"iti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"tisu","osnova2":"u","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"tre","osnova2":"aš","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"tre","osnova2":"ašev","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"tre","osnova2":"ašica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"tre","osnova2":"ašičin-","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"tre","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"tre","osnova2":"ina","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"trokuti","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"trudno","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"tu","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"u","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"uop","osnova2":"e","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"upu","osnova2":"enost","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"uš","osnova2":"e","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"uve","osnova2":"anica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"valjči","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"ve","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"ve","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"ve","osnova2":"ina","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"vije","osnova2":"e","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"vo","osnova2":"arna","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"vo","osnova2":"arnica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"vo","osnova2":"e","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"vo","osnova2":"ka","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"vo","osnova2":"ni","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"vo","osnova2":"njak","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"vra","osnova2":"ati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"vre","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"vrti","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"vru","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"vru","osnova2":"e","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"vru","osnova2":"ica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"vru","osnova2":"ina","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"vuči","osnova2":"-","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"vu","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"zada","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"zeči","osnova2":"-","glagol":"","pin":"",},
], 
 
 p3 = [{"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["dž","đ"],"osnova":"﻿deter","osnova2":"ent","glagol":"","pin":"",},
 {"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["dž","đ"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"amija","glagol":"","pin":"",},
 {"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["dž","đ"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"em","glagol":"","pin":"",},
 {"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["dž","đ"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"emper","glagol":"","pin":"",},
 {"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["dž","đ"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"ep","glagol":"","pin":"",},
 {"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["dž","đ"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"eparac","glagol":"","pin":"",},
 {"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["dž","đ"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"epić","glagol":"","pin":"",},
 {"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["dž","đ"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"ez","glagol":"","pin":"",},
 {"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["dž","đ"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"ip","glagol":"","pin":"",},
 {"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["dž","đ"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"ul","glagol":"","pin":"",},
 {"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["dž","đ"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"ungla","glagol":"","pin":"",},
 {"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["dž","đ"],"osnova":"fi","osnova2":"ijski","glagol":"","pin":"",},
 {"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["dž","đ"],"osnova":"ho","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
 {"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["dž","đ"],"osnova":"kambo","osnova2":"anski","glagol":"","pin":"",},
 {"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["dž","đ"],"osnova":"mahara","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
 {"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["dž","đ"],"osnova":"mena","osnova2":"er","glagol":"","pin":"",},
 {"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["dž","đ"],"osnova":"mena","osnova2":"erica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
 {"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["dž","đ"],"osnova":"mena","osnova2":"eričin","glagol":"","pin":"",},
 {"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["dž","đ"],"osnova":"mena","osnova2":"erov","glagol":"","pin":"",},
 {"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["dž","đ"],"osnova":"mena","osnova2":"erski","glagol":"","pin":"",},
 {"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["dž","đ"],"osnova":"naru","osnova2":"ba","glagol":"","pin":"",},
 {"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["dž","đ"],"osnova":"pan","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
 {"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["dž","đ"],"osnova":"patli","osnova2":"an","glagol":"","pin":"",},
 {"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["dž","đ"],"osnova":"pi","osnova2":"ama","glagol":"","pin":"",},
 {"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["dž","đ"],"osnova":"u","osnova2":"benik","glagol":"","pin":"",},
 {"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"an","osnova2":"elov","glagol":"","pin":"",},
 {"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"an","osnova2":"eo","glagol":"","pin":"",},
 {"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"an","osnova2":"eoski","glagol":"","pin":"",},
 {"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"arkan","osnova2":"elov","glagol":"","pin":"",},
 {"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"arkan","osnova2":"eo","glagol":"","pin":"",},
 {"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"bu","osnova2":"enje","glagol":"","pin":"",},
 {"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"doga","osnova2":"aj","glagol":"","pin":"",},
 {"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"doga","osnova2":"anje","glagol":"","pin":"",},
 {"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"doga","osnova2":"ati se","glagol":"","pin":"",},
 {"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"dosa","osnova2":"ivati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
 {"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"dovi","osnova2":"enja","glagol":"","pin":"",},
 {"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"ak","glagol":"","pin":"",},
 {"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"akovački","glagol":"","pin":"",},
 {"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"avao","glagol":"","pin":"",},
 {"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"avolak","glagol":"","pin":"",},
 {"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"avolčev","glagol":"","pin":"",},
 {"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"avolčić","glagol":"","pin":"",},
 {"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"avolčićev","glagol":"","pin":"",},
 {"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"avolica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
 {"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"avoličin","glagol":"","pin":"",},
 {"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"avolov","glagol":"","pin":"",},
 {"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"avolski","glagol":"","pin":"",},
 {"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"iha","glagol":"","pin":"",},
 {"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"on","glagol":"","pin":"",},
 {"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"umbir","glagol":"","pin":"",},
 {"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"ur","glagol":"","pin":"",},
 {"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"ur","glagol":"","pin":"",},
 {"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"g","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
 {"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"g","osnova2":"ica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
 {"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"gospo","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
 {"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"gospo","osnova2":"ica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
 {"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"gove","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
 {"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"gra","osnova2":"anin","glagol":"","pin":"",},
 {"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"gra","osnova2":"evina","glagol":"","pin":"",},
 {"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"grož","osnova2":"e","glagol":"","pin":"",},
 {"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"gun","osnova2":"ati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
 {"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"izme","osnova2":"u","glagol":"","pin":"",},
 {"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"iznena","osnova2":"enje","glagol":"","pin":"",},
 {"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"iznena","osnova2":"ivati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
 {"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"kra","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
 {"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"la","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
 {"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"le","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
 {"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"ma","osnova2":"arski","glagol":"","pin":"",},
 {"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"ma","osnova2":"ioničar","glagol":"","pin":"",},
 {"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"ma","osnova2":"ioničarev","glagol":"","pin":"",},
 {"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"ma","osnova2":"ioničarka","glagol":"","pin":"",},
 {"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"ma","osnova2":"ioničarkin","glagol":"","pin":"",},
 {"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"ma","osnova2":"ioničarov","glagol":"","pin":"",},
 {"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"ma","osnova2":"ioničarski","glagol":"","pin":"",},
 {"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"me","osnova2":"imurski","glagol":"","pin":"",},
 {"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"me","osnova2":"u","glagol":"","pin":"",},
 {"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"me","osnova2":"unarodni","glagol":"","pin":"",},
 {"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"me","osnova2":"uspremnik","glagol":"","pin":"",},
 {"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"me","osnova2":"utim","glagol":"","pin":"",},
 {"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"novoro","osnova2":"enče","glagol":"","pin":"",},
 {"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"odre","osnova2":"en","glagol":"","pin":"",},
 {"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"odre","osnova2":"eno","glagol":"","pin":"",},
 {"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"odre","osnova2":"ivati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
 {"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"oru","osnova2":"e","glagol":"","pin":"",},
 {"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"poga","osnova2":"ati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
 {"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"poro","osnova2":"aj","glagol":"","pin":"",},
 {"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"posu","osnova2":"e","glagol":"","pin":"",},
 {"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"posu","osnova2":"enica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
 {"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"posu","osnova2":"ivati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
 {"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"posva","osnova2":"ati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
 {"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"preure","osnova2":"ivati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
 {"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"proizvo","osnova2":"ač","glagol":"","pin":"",},
 {"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"proizvo","osnova2":"ačica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
 {"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"proizvo","osnova2":"ačičin","glagol":"","pin":"",},
 {"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"ra","osnova2":"aona","glagol":"","pin":"",},
 {"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"ra","osnova2":"aonica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
 {"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"ra","osnova2":"ati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
 {"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"ri","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
 {"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"ro","osnova2":".","glagol":"","pin":"",},
 {"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"ro","osnova2":"ački","glagol":"","pin":"",},
 {"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"ro","osnova2":"ak","glagol":"","pin":"",},
 {"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"ro","osnova2":"akinja","glagol":"","pin":"",},
 {"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"ro","osnova2":"akinjin","glagol":"","pin":"",},
 {"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"ro","osnova2":"akov","glagol":"","pin":"",},
 {"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"ro","osnova2":"endan","glagol":"","pin":"",},
 {"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"ro","osnova2":"endanski","glagol":"","pin":"",},
 {"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"ro","osnova2":"enje","glagol":"","pin":"",},
 {"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"sme","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
 {"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"sme","osnova2":"e","glagol":"","pin":"",},
 {"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"strojovo","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
 {"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"su","osnova2":"e","glagol":"","pin":"",},
 {"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"sura","osnova2":"ivati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
 {"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"sva","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
 {"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"sva","osnova2":"ati se","glagol":"","pin":"",},
 {"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"svi","osnova2":"ati se","glagol":"","pin":"",},
 {"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"tako","osnova2":"er","glagol":"","pin":"",},
 {"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"tu","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
 {"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"tu","osnova2":"e","glagol":"","pin":"",},
 {"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"tvr","osnova2":"ava","glagol":"","pin":"",},
 {"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"ure","osnova2":"aj","glagol":"","pin":"",},
 {"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"ure","osnova2":"ivač","glagol":"","pin":"",},
 {"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"ure","osnova2":"ivati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
 {"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"uspore","osnova2":"ivati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
 {"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"vojvo","osnova2":"anski","glagol":"","pin":"",},
 {"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"že","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
 {"question":"popuni","hint":"dž/đ","correctAnswer":["đ","dž"],"osnova":"že","osnova2":"ati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
 ];